{
  "1_Oude_Sterrenwacht": {
    "checkin_question": " There is a clock in front of the entrance. What does the text say below this clock?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "Wintertijd",
      "Zomertijd",
      "Ruimtetijd",
      "Tijd"
    ],
    "post_check": "This is the Old Observatory in Leiden, the former site of all astronomy-related research performed in Leiden – and the start of your adventure!",
    "checkin_answer": "Zomertijd",
    "astro_question": "What surface area does the ALMA cover?",
    "astro_options": [
      "1 square km",
      "5 square km",
      "20 square km",
      "100 square km"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "20 square km"
  },
  "2_Doelenpoort": {
    "checkin_question": "How many barrels can you find on the gate?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "4",
    "post_check": "A gate from 1645, dedicated to the soldiers of Leiden. The sun is depicted multiple times on this gate. How many suns can you find?",
    "astro_question": "How many telescopes does the ALMA have?",
    "astro_options": [
      "8",
      "24",
      "42",
      "66"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "66"
  },
  "3_Sieboldhuis": {
    "checkin_question": "What shape does the window above the door have?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "Square",
      "Round",
      "Triangle",
      "Star"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "Round",
    "post_check": "This is a museum about Japan-related research in Leiden. Japanese astronomers also make use of ALMA: a true international collaboration!",
    "astro_question": "Which institutes work on the ALMA together? ",
    "astro_options": [
      "A and B",
      "A and D",
      "B and D",
      "A, B, C",
      "All of them"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "All of them"
  },
  "4_Molen_de_Put": {
    "checkin_question": "From what year is the original windmill?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "1612",
      "1617",
      "1619",
      "1624"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "1619",
    "post_check": "This is one of two windmills you will encounter on your adventure. Their blades remind us of the round telescope dishes at ALMA.",
    "astro_question": "How large is one ALMA telescope dish compared to the blades of this mill?",
    "astro_options": [
      "0.5 times as large",
      "Equal in size",
      "Twice as large",
      "Ten times as large"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "0.5 times as large"
  },
  "5_Museum_Volkenkunde": {
    "checkin_question": "What name does the café across from Museum Volkenkunde have?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "Stadscafé Van der Werff",
      "Studio de Veste",
      "De Bruine Boon",
      "Restaurant De Valk"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "Stadscafé Van der Werff",
    "post_check": "Step into the courtyard of this large museum to get a taste of what they offer.",
    "astro_question": "",
    "astro_options": [
      "Found it!"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "Found it!"
  },
  "6_Molen_de_Valk": {
    "checkin_question": "What year was the windmill built?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "1743",
      "1746",
      "1750",
      "1755"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "1743",
    "post_check": "This windmill is larger than the previous one you saw. Just like these windmills, not all telescopes at ALMA are equal in size and diameter.",
    "astro_question": "Which of the following is not a type of star?",
    "astro_options": [
      "Brown Dwarf",
      "Hypergiant",
      "Neutron Star",
      "White Dwarf"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "Brown Dwarf"
  },
  "7_Museum_de_Lakenhal": {
    "checkin_question": "Above the entrance gate is a small statue of what?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "Gargoyle",
      "Telescope",
      "Lion",
      "Windmill"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "Windmill",
    "post_check": "If the door is open, we recommend you step into the pretty courtyard and take a look!",
    "astro_question": "At the end of its lifetime, the sun will become a red giant. How large will its diameter be, compared to its current size?",
    "astro_options": [
      "2x",
      "20x",
      "200x",
      "2000x"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "200x"
  },
  "8_Leidse_schouwburg": {
    "checkin_question": "How many lamps can you find hanging on the side the building?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "4",
    "post_check": "You're halfway there now!",
    "astro_question": "This picture was made with ALMA. What is this image of?",
    "astro_options": [
      "Jupiter",
      "Neptune",
      "The sun",
      "Another star"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  "9_Rijksmuseum_Boerhaave": {
    "checkin_question": "Beside the museum, a formula is painted on the wall. What is the leftmost letter of the formula?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "R",
      "G",
      "F",
      "A"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "R",
    "post_check": "This equation is Einstein's field equation: it describes how objects distort the space around them. This physics equation has proved to be very important in astronomy. Next to the equation, you will find Museum Boerhaave. This museum displays a large collection of scientific objects, including a significant collection of astronomy-related objects. It's definitely worth a visit on a rainy day!",
    "astro_question": "Galileo Galilei was a famous astronomer. Which of the following discoveries did he make?",
    "astro_options": [
      "He invented the telescope.",
      "He discovered that the earth orbited the sun, and not the other way around.",
      "He saw that Jupiter had four moons of its own.",
      "He proclaimed the existence of the planet Neptune."
    ],
    "astro_answer": "He saw that Jupiter had four moons of its own."
  },
  "10_Burcht": {
    "checkin_question": ": How many stars can you, at most, find on a single shield?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "3",
    "post_check": "Situated on a hill, the Burcht is the highest point of Leiden - though not as high up as ALMA...",
    "astro_question": "Why is ALMA located at the Atacama Desert at 5000 meters altitude?",
    "astro_options": [
      "In the mountains, the air is thinner clearer, so you have a better view of the stars.",
      "The Atacama Desert is very dry, with very little water vapor in the air.",
      "The nearest city is very far away, so there are no unwanted visitors.",
      "There is no snow in the desert, which would distort astronomical measurements."
    ],
    "astro_answer": "The Atacama Desert is very dry, with very little water vapor in the air."
  },
  "11_Hooglandse_Kerk": {
    "checkin_question": "When was the original wooden chapel built on this location?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "1300",
      "1307",
      "1314",
      "1321"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "1314",
    "post_check": "One of Leiden's largest and oldest churches.",
    "astro_question": "Play with the constellations in the flyer.",
    "astro_options": [
      "Done!"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "Done!"
  },
  "12_Plaatsteeg_20": {
    "checkin_question": "On this tower, you will find a formula. Whose formula is this? ",
    "checkin_options": [
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Christiaan Huygens",
      "Herman Boerhaave",
      "Galileo Galilei"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "Christiaan Huygens",
    "post_check": "",
    "astro_question": "How many galaxies are estimated to be in the observable universe?",
    "astro_options": [
      "2 billion",
      "20 billion",
      "2 trillion",
      "200 trillion"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "2 trillion"
  },
  "13_Pieterskerkhof_40": {
    "checkin_question": "At this address, you will find an old house. How many heads are on the façade?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "6"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "6",
    "post_check": "This house is where the Leiden mathematician Snellius was born. He also wrote two works on astronomy. ",
    "astro_question": "This is a photograph of a galaxy. What was the image of ALMA?",
    "astro_options": [
      "A",
      "B",
      "C"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "B"
  },
  "14_Kamerlingh_Onnes_Gebouw": {
    "checkin_question": "What quote from Heike Kamerlingh Onnes can you find outside the entrance?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "Door meten tot weten",
      "Met meten tot weten",
      "Meten en weten",
      "Door meten naar weten"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "Door meten tot weten",
    "post_check": " In this building, Heike Kamerlingh Onnes first created liquid helium. The telescopes at ALMA actually need liquid helium to work!",
    "astro_question": "follow the mysterious animal tracks in the flyer.",
    "astro_options": [
      "Done!"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "Done!"
  },
  "15_Koepoortsbrug": {
    "checkin_question": "How many bridges lie between here and the Old Observatory?",
    "checkin_options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "checkin_answer": "1",
    "post_check": "Nearly there!",
    "astro_question": "What galaxy did you find?",
    "astro_options": [
      "Andromeda",
      "Milky Way",
      "Pinwheel galaxy",
      "Sombrero galaxy",
      "Whirlpool galaxy"
    ],
    "astro_answer": "Whirlpool galaxy"
  }
}